Guide to the John E. Nance papers, 1960-1990.
Nance, John E. papers
- Series II: Photographic materials
  - Map and photographs, Philippines (photos), 1977 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Associated Press photos, Bullit Marquez (photos), 1987 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Cross country, Bill Furgeson, Gresham (negatives), 1999 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Tasaday, Black and White Prints (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Friends of the Tasaday (photos) (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Duplicates from Tasaday book (photos) (Box 23, Folder 24-26)
  - 1971 Bob Fox Prints of Tasaday, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Tasaday 1986 (contact sheets), 1986 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Unused Elizalde for Book (photos), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Tasaday contact sheets Tas 1986 17-1 to 17-26, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Loose Material 1 (Contact sheets), [N.D.] (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Tasaday Contact Sheets of 201 to 285 (270 and 281 missing), [N.D.] (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Contact Sheets 101 to 122, [N.D.] (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Tasaday 300 to 310 (Contact sheets), [N.D.] (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Tasaday T401-405/Contacts, [N.D.] (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Tasaday 500 to 517 (Contact sheets), [N.D.] (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - T 602 to 619 (Contact sheets), [N.D.] (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Tasaday T-850-852 (Contact sheets), [N.D.] (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - T 901 to 910 (Contact sheets), [N.D.] (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Tasaday Contact Sheets 1001 to 1007 (Contact sheets), [N.D.] (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - T-1100-1110 (Contact sheets), [N.D.] (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Eibesfeldt? w/ T'boli/Blit 1974 (plus others). D-1, TR-2, X-1 (T'boli, dances, Mai, Bic, (Ana laughing?)), 1974 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Blit Contacts B.D.E.J.K, [N.D.] (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Tasaday photos in Escape magazine (misc. formats), 1998 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - 1989 to be Printed (misc formats), 1997 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Tasaday B&W Lake Sebu April 2001, T-2001-8 thru T2001-12 and Manila and PDX-gNN's Cat(?), 2001 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - B&W Negs-No Contacts. Tasaday, Philippines, Elizalde, Manila 1987., 1987-1997 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - B&W Negs Philippines 1987, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Tasaday B&W Lake Sebu April 2001, T-2001-1 thru 2001-7 (negatives, contact sheets), 2001 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Black and White Prints 2001 visit with Tasaday, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Color Negs/Prints Tasaday/Elizalde, etc. 1987 Manila, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Tasaday Negs April 2000, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Tasaday Lake Sebu 15-19 April 2001 TC 2001 E-L (negatives, prints), 2001 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - WM Stafford at Menucha 1982 (misc formats), 1982 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Loose Material 2 (color prints), [N.D.] (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Tasaday (negatives) (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Tasaday contact sheets (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Vietnam article photographs (2), 1966 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Egypt Contact sheets (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Formosa (photos and negatives) (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Unlabeled photographs (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Bulacan Beach, Kemato, etc. (photos) (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Tasaday with descriptive labels (photos), 1997 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Contact Sheets (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Photographs glued on paper sheets (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Negative Tasaday prints, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Negative Lindbergh prints, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Lindbergh Symposium, 2002-2004 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Lindbergh Foundation, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Lindbergh childhood home, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Aerospace Museum, Lindbergh Display, Balboa Park, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Lindbergh house, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Tasaday Mapmaking (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Tasaday in truck headed home, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Adug/Guintuy in truck/Helbury Dance Troupe, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Unlabeled photographs (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Photos from Jerry Jones, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Color negatives (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Bus to Gen San, Manila, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Tasaday ride bus top and plant nursery, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Tasaday in Longhouse, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Tasaday, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Tasaday start for home in truck, some carrying seedlings, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Tasaday, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Cuts of photographs (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Contact Sheets (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Tasaday large prints with descriptions (Box 25, Folder 20-21)
  - Zagreb, Frankfurt, Thailand, MLA (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - House photos, Reynolds (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Sunset photographs, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Art Exhibit, World's Fair, Mary Hurst (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Personal Film (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Pruitt's Wedding (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Family births, MLA, birthdays (Box 25, Folder 28-29)
  - N.G. Photographs, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 30-31)
  - Nance trip-odds and ends (Box 25, Folder 32-33)
  - Miscellaneous unlabeled, 1960s (Box 26, Folder 1-4)
  - Mom and Dad's 50th anniversary, Christmas, GJN (Box 26, Folder 5-6)
  - Pacific (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Tasaday Forest photographs, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Tasaday (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Copies of Tasaday, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Michael at Tasaday, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Tasaday contact sheet, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Lobo of the Tasaday photographs and slides (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Tasaday contact sheet, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Tasaday, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 15-17)
  - Tasaday contact sheet, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Wounded Family in war zone photographs, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Girl and grandmother capture in Delta Village (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Lindbergh copy negatives (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Vietnam (negatives) (Box 26, Folder 22-23)
  - Boy with wounded hand (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous village kids, GI's with body bags, face of tunnel rat (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Unlabeled (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Tasaday photographs and captions (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Cuts, Vietnam (Box 26, Folder 28-29)
  - Negatives, Vietnam, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 1-7)
  - Unlabeled (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Family photographs, Vietnam, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Vietnam (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Photos from Vietnam for use from original Saigon, contact sheets (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Panamin helicopter (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Vietnam, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 13-15)
  - Associated press (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Unlabeled photographs (Box 28, Folder 1-3)
  - 32nd Rangers My Tho (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Lobo (Box 28, Folder 5-6)
  - Unused Lobo (Box 28, Folder 7-8)
  - Poor quality duplicates from GT (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Tasaday, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Tasaday, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Tasaday, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Manila, non-Tasaday, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Tasaday, color, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Unlabeled Photographs, 1986-1989 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - unlabeled negatives, 1976-1989 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Elizalde (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Tasaday, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Unlabeled, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Tasaday at Kemato (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Tasaday, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Tasaday (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Tasaday with labels, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Original prints from Discovery of the Tasaday, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 12-14)
  - Original prints from the Gentle Tasaday (Box 29, Folder 15-16)
  - Tasaday set, 1970s (Box 29, Folder 17-18)
  - Unlabeled photographs (Box 29, Folder 19-21)
  - Nance contact sheets (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Banawe (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Vietnam notebooks (Box 30, Folder 1-6)
  - Sketches of pages (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Contact sheets, negatives (Box 30, Folder 8-10)
  - Negative strip (Box 30)
  - Blank or Undeveloped film (Box 30)
  - Unlabeled negative rolls (Box 30)
  - camera film canisters (Box 30)
  - DVDs of scanned photographs, DVD-1044-1048 (Box 30)
  - Large Tasaday prints (Box 38)
  - Scrap book (Box 39)
  - Matted Tasaday prints (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Large Tasaday prints (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Series III. Video
  Includes videos on the Tasaday. VHS, DVD and film.
  - Montessori Christmas, 8mm, F-700 (Box 30)
  - Tasaday, Message from the Stone Age, DVD-922, 923 (Box 30)
  - Elizalde Costa Rica/Miami Video Cassettes, Umatic S, 1986; V-6729-6730 (Box 31)
  - Today Show "Cave People" Video Cassette, Umatic, 1975; V-6731 (Box 31)
  - Today Show "Cave People" 2-inch Quad Videotape, 1975; V-6992 (Box 31)
  - Tasaday Segment for To Tell The Truth (TTTT) 2" quad videotape, 1975; V-6995 (Box 31)
  - Tasaday Segment for TTTT 2" quad videotape, 1975; V-6994 (Box 31)
  - Tasaday Freeze Frame, 4 Segments (for TTTT) 2" quad videotape, 1975; V-6993 (Box 31)
  - Ft St Weekly Video Cassette, Umatic, 1984; V-6732 (Box 31)
  - Tasaday at Kemato with J Nance Tape 1, [N.D.]; V-6735 (Box 32)
  - Tasaday at Kemato with J Nance Tape 2, [N.D.]; V-6736 (Box 32)
  - Tasaday at Kemato with J Nance Tape 3, [N.D.]; V-6737 (Box 32)
  - Tasaday at Kemato with J Nance Tape 4, [N.D.]; V-6738 (Box 32)
  - Tasaday at Kemato with J Nance Tape 5, [N.D.]; V-6739 (Box 32)
  - Tasaday at Kemato with J Nance Tape 6, [N.D.]; V-6740 (Box 32)
  - Tasaday at Kemato with J Nance Tape 6A, [N.D.]; V-6741 (Box 32)
  - Tasaday at Kemato with J Nance Tape 7, [N.D.]; V-6742 (Box 32)
  - Tasaday at Kemato with J Nance Tape 8, [N.D.]; V-6743 (Box 32)
  - A Message from the Stone Age by John Nance, [N.D.]; V-6733 (Box 32)
  - Tasaday Interviews at Kematu, [N.D.]; V-6734 (Box 32)
  - Tasaday Interviews at Kematu, [N.D.]; V-6744 (Box 32)
  - Jen and Clark, V-6759 (Box 33)
  - BBC Tasaday: Trith of Hoax, 1989; V-6760 (Box 33)
  - Last Tribe of Mindanao, V-6761 (Box 33)
  - Tasaday on Mindanao, 1988; V-6762 (Box 33)
  - Jen Tasaday, V-6763 (Box 33)
  - Dula at lake Sebu hearing, 1987; V-6764-6774 (Box 33)
  - Tasaday with Nance, V-6775-6778 (Box 33)
  - International forum on the Tasaday controversy, V-6779 (Box 33)
  - the Bitter End, V-6780 (Box 33)
  - Happy Birthday Mom Dakel Diwata, 1988; V-6781 (Box 33)
  - First Tasaday visit to White Plains, 1989; V-6782 (Box 33)
  - Tasaday, Jack Reynolds, V-6783 (Box 33)
  - Edited News, Galang, 1988; V-6784 (Box 33)
  - Twilight of Tasaday Peoples, 1988; V-6785-6786 (Box 33)
  - A Man with Many Names, V-6787 (Box 33)
  - Roller Skate and Motorcycles with Tasaday, 1988; V-6788 (Box 33)
  - Tasaday at Kematu, 1988; V-6789-6795 (Box 33)
  - Nightly News, 1988; V-6796 (Box 33)
  - "The Fifth Estate" Caveman or Con Man? ", 1990; V-6797 (Box 33)
  - John Nance lecture, Dr. Harris Class, 1990; V-6798 (Box 33)
  - Reply to 20-20, V-6799 (Box 33)
  - "First Contact", V-6800 (Box 33)
  - Tasaday, Jack Reynolds, 1986; V-6801 (Box 33)
  - Lakers Game, V-6802 (Box 33)
  - Tasaday: Fake or Real, V-6803 (Box 33)
  - Anthropological Congress, UP, 1986; V-6804-6805 (Box 34)
  - Tribesman Identify, V-6806-6807 (Box 34)
  - Edited Master, "Fiesta in Lake Sebu", V-6808 (Box 34)
  - RTVMCI, V-6809 (Box 34)
  - Mayor Mondragon's Statements, V-6810 (Box 34)
  - Datu Galang, V-6811 (Box 34)
  - Tasaday reply to 20/20, V-6812 (Box 34)
  - Edited Material, APOG making, V-6813 (Box 34)
  - Hearing of National Cultural Minorities, V-6814-6817 (Box 34)
  - Tasaday Hearing: National Cultural Minorities Congress, December 10, 1987; V-6747-6755 (Box 35)
  - Anthropological Congress in UP, 1986; V-6756 (Box 35)
- Series IV. Audio
  Includes recordings of Nance’s interviews with Tasaday, and other audio related audio material. On cassette and microcassette.
  - Tasaday, Manila, White Plains, Elizalde, December 6, 1987; TR-9718-9719 (Box 36)
  - Dula, congress questioning, December 10, 1987; TR-9720-9722 (Box 36)
  - Stewart Rosenberg, Tasaday discussion, TR-9723 (Box 36)
  - Zagreb Tasaday symposium, July 1988; TR-9724-9726 (Box 36)
  - Judith Moses, Al Spileski, 1986; TR-9727 (Box 36)
  - Tasaday at Cares, 1986; TR-9728 (Box 36)
  - Mindanao, T'Boli, TR-9729 (Box 36)
  - Dad Tuan interview, May 8, 1986; TR-9730-9731 (Box 36)
  - Jerry Malayong interview, April 28, 1986; TR-9732 (Box 36)
  - International Conference of the Tasaday, August 1986; TR-9733-9735 (Box 36)
  - Tasaday at T'boli, Mindinao, April 1986; TR-9376-9738 (Box 36)
  - Tasaday dance, sunrise, May 1986; TR-9739 (Box 36)
  - Tasaday visit, Joh Reynolds interview, May 1986; TR-9740-9741 (Box 36)
  - Elizalde, 1987; TR-9742 (Box 36)
  - Carlos Fernandez congressional testimony, December 1987; TR-9743 (Box 36)
  - John Reynolds interview, TR-9744-9747 (Box 36)
  - Blahing tells of Mark's visit, 1986; TR-9748 (Box 36)
  - Dafal interviews, T'Boli, Mindanao, Kematu, 1986; TR-9749-9750 (Box 36)
  - There is no tape with this number, TR-9751. (Box 36)
  - T'Boli, Mindanao, 1986; TR-9752 (Box 36)
  - Manila Tasaday Conference, 1986; TR-9753-9754 (Box 36)
  - John Nance at Catlin, TR-9755 (Box 36)
  - The Gentle Tasaday interview by Susan Butruille, 1978; TR-9756 (Box 36)
  - Sounds off NBC Tasaday, TR-9757 (Box 36)
  - Interview with John Nance WUTC, 1990; TR-9758 (Box 36)
  - Tasaday Tape, Manila, 1987; TR_9759-9763 (Box 36)
  - Dad Tuan interview, 1986; TR-9764-9766 (Box 36)
  - Chicago Tasaday discussion, 1991; TR-9769 (Box 36)
  - WBEZ by the hour, 1991; TR-9770 (Box 36)
  - Al Speleski, Manila, 1986; TR-9771 (Box 36)
  - Judith Moses, 1986; TR-9772 (Box 36)
  - M.E. Jr Interview, TR-9773 (Box 36)
  - Interview with Jerry Malayang, with Nance, Manila, April 28, 1986; TR-9774-9775 (Box 36)
  - Tasaday Tape, Manila, 1987; TR_9776,TR-9803 (Box 36)
  - Tasaday, bird calls, 1972; TR-9777 (Box 36)
  - Tasaday forest, 1972; TR-9778 (Box 36)
  - Tasaday tapes, December 1987; TR-9779-9782 (Box 36)
  - Mindanao talks, April 1986; TR-9783-9784 (Box 36)
  - Tasaday controversy, 1989; TR_9785-9788 (Box 36)
  - Tasaday tapes, 1988; TR-9789-9797,TR-9802 (Box 36)
  - Tasaday, Edith Terry, TR-9798 (Box 36)
  - Tasaday bird calls, TR-9799 (Box 36)
  - Tasaday Tape, 1986; TR-9800 (Box 36)
  - Tasaday tape, evening at the cave, 1972; TR-9801 (Box 36)
  - Yen on Tasaday, TR-9804 (Box 36)
  - Blit music, 1972; TR-9805-9806 (Box 36)
  - Yen and Nance, TR-9807 (Box 36)
  - Manila (microcassette), TR-9808 (Box 36)
  - Tasaday at Kematu (microcassette), 1988; TR-9809-9816 (Box 36)
  - Tasaday interviews (microcassette), TR-9817-9825 (Box 36)
  - Buddhist chants (microcassette), 1994; TR-9826 (Box 36)
  - AAA Tasaday (microcassette), TR-9827-9831 (Box 36)
  - Zagrieb (microcassette), 1988; TR-9832-9835 (Box 36)
  - Dad Tuan (microcassette), 1986; TR-9836-9838 (Box 36)
  - Dula (microcassette), 1987; Tr-9839-9843 (Box 36)
  - Conversational dul (microcassette), 1997; TR-9844 (Box 36)
  - Interview segments (microcassette), 1987; TR-9845-9847 (Box 36)
  - Unlabeled/illegible (microcassette), TR-9848-9858 (Box 36)